<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Three Houses Info</string>
    <string name="general_information">General Information</string>
    <string name="my_playthrough">My Playthrough</string>
    <string name="playthough_button_background">Playthough Button Background</string>
    <string name="players_house_choice">Player\'s house choice</string>
    <!--Character Descriptions-->
    <string name="byleth_description">Originally a member of a mercenary band led by their father, Jeralt. However when they rescued students from the Officer’s Academy from bandits, their unique power was recognised and they were invited to become a teacher at the Garreg-Mach Monastery. Can be male or female.</string>
    <string name="sothis_description">An enigmatic being that appeared in the protagonist’s dreams. After saving the protagonist with the power to rewind time, she speaks to them as if she’s inside their head, yet nobody else can see or hear her. She has no recollection of her identity and has the body of a young girl, but the tone of an old lady.</string>
    <string name="edelgard_description">The imperial princess of the Adrestian Empire–a mighty nation with a rich history–and its next emperor. Within the Black Eagles, she’s the house leader. She has an extremely noble and dignified air to her, and is able to calmly assess and act upon the situation and the people around her.</string>
    <string name="hubert_description">The strategist of the Black Eagles. He’s the heir of Marquis Vestra’s family and has served Edelgard from a young age. He’ll use any means necessary to eliminate her obstacles. According to Edelgard, he’s a cold, but reasonable person.</string>
    <string name="dorothea_description">A female student who was a popular songstress in the imperial capital before she enrolled. She admires Manuela, who came from the same Mittelfrank opera company, as her senior. Within the Black Eagles, she’s the only commoner, which makes her feel uneasy, but she treats all of her similarly aged friends as equals.</string>
    <string name="ferdinand_description">The heir of Duke Aegir’s family–a renowned family where the title of imperial chancellor is passed down. He’s very proud of his own family because of its importance and influence. Extremely confident and hates to lose. Princess Edelgard’s brilliance ignites a sense of rivalry within him.</string>
    <string name="bernadetta_description">The only daughter of Count Varley’s family. She’s abnormally shy and, while she’s far from home, her one safe haven is her room in the dormitory. Except for during lectures, she tends to confine herself to her room, devoting herself to her pastimes.</string>
    <string name="caspar_description">The second son of Count Bergliez’s family. Since he’s not in line to succeed his family, he decided to train at the Officer’s Academy to become a successful martial artist. His quick temper is his only flaw; otherwise he has a keen sense of justice that despises lies and injustice, and is a honest and straightforward guy.</string>
    <string name="petra_description">The granddaughter of the king of the Brigid Isles, a group of islands located west from Fódlan’s shores. Because Brigid is a vassal of the empire, as a symbol of loyalty, she was sent from her homeland to study abroad at the Officer’s Academy. She’s unaccustomed to the spoken language of Fódlan, but she is trying her best to learn.</string>
    <string name="linhardt_description">The heir of Count Hevring’s family. He prefers freedom over restriction; one could also call him incredibly lazy, as despite his brilliant mind, he’s always sleepy. However, he has a keen interest in crest research, to the point that he’ll forget to eat or sleep. Although he and Caspar have very different tastes and personalities, they somehow get along.</string>
    <string name="dimitri_description">The next king of the Holy Kingdom of Faerghus, the realm of noble knights, and the house leader of the Blue Lions. He’s a sincere young man who embodies chivalry, but at times, a faint shadow can be felt behind his cheeriness.</string>
    <string name="dedue_description">A commoner born in the Duscur region, to the kingdom’s north-west, and Dimitri’s servant. He owes a great debt to Dimitri and is determined to protect him at the cost of his own life. Because he’s a bit scary-looking and quiet, many people don’t realise he’s actually a gentle and nice young man.</string>
    <string name="felix_description">The heir of Duke Fraldarius’s family. He has a mean attitude, calling his childhood buddy Dimitri a “boar”. He’s sarcastic and fashions himself a lone wolf, but he takes his sword training seriously, so much that he’ll instantly challenge any strong person to a bout.</string>
    <string name="mercedes_description">A kind woman who carefully observes her surroundings and cannot ignore people in need. She’s a former imperial noble, but now lives as a commoner in the kingdom. Earlier, she was enrolled in the royal capital’s magic academy. Claims to be a “little older” than the other students.</string>
    <string name="ashe_description">The adopted son of Lord Lonato, ruler of Gaspard Castle within the kingdom. He feels immense gratitude and respect for Sir Lonato, who adopted him as a child despite being a commoner and allowed him to enroll in the Officer’s Academy. He’s a serious young man who studies and trains diligently to become an admirable adult like his adoptive father.</string>
    <string name="anette_description">The niece of Baron Dominic. She graduated from the Magic Academy in the Royal Capital with flying colours. She’s cheerful and hard-working, but she can often waste her energy and end up nowhere. Mercedes is a close friend of hers from her Magic Academy days; the pair call each other “Mercie” and “Ann”.</string>
    <string name="sylvain_description">The heir of Margrave Gautier who rules near the borders. He values his friends, and is widely looked up as a dependable “big brother” by the other classmates. Yet at the same time, he’s a hopeless womaniser who loves flirting with girls, which causes him no end of trouble. He had an older brother who was disowned because he lacked a crest.</string>
    <string name="ingrid_description">A lady from Count Galatea’s family; Dimitri, Felix, Sylvain and her are all childhood friends. Seeing her serious attitude and admiration of virtuous knights, Dimitri would always say “you’re more of a knight than you think”. However, once she lays eyes on delicious food, she’d forget everything.</string>
    <string name="claude_description"> He’s the heir of the renowned Riegan family, which heads the Leicester Alliance, a new power formed by the nobility. Serves as the house leader of the Golden Deer. While he’s memorable for his sociable smile and easy-going attitude, he also harbours a cunning side, calling himself someone with an “overly perceptive mind”.</string>
    <string name="lorenz_description">The heir of Count Gloucester’s family. He’s a serious fellow despite his snobbishness and he’s aware of his pride and responsibility as a noble. Apparently, he’s been approaching several females at the monastery, with limited success.</string>
    <string name="hilda_description">The only daughter of Duke Goneril. Since she was pampered by her father and older brother, she tends to slack off, and is good at acting cute and buttering people up. She has a easy-going and frivolous manner, and is a typical “nobleman’s daughter”. Adores fashionable and glamorous things.</string>
    <string name="raphael_description">The son of a merchant from Leicester. Both of his parents died in an accident and he’s been through a lot, but he’s an optimistic fellow who’s only concerned about what’s on the menu and his daily muscle-building to become an exemplary knight. That said, he doesn’t seem interested in lectures.</string>
    <string name="lysithea_description">The eldest daughter of Count Ordelia’s family. She’s the youngest student enrolled this year, at 15 years of age. She’s a child prodigy who excels at magic, yet she’s a hard worker who doesn’t make a fuss about her talent. Despite that, she still has a childish side, not wanting to be seen as a child and having a fear of ghosts.</string>
    <string name="ignatz_description">The second son of a merchant family within the Leicester Alliance. His older brother is set to take over the family business, so his parents wished for him to enter the Officer’s Academy, although deep down there are other things he’d rather be doing. He’s a kind-hearted person who loves beautiful natural scenery and art.</string>
    <string name="marianne_description">The adopted daughter of Margrave Edmund who rules near the borders. She tends not to associate with others, so there many people who have yet to hear her voice. On the other hand, she adores birds and animals and can talk very openly to them. She is extremely devout and offers prayers to the Goddess everyday</string>
    <string name="leonie_description">A hunter’s daughter from Sauin Village, within the alliance. To become a money-making mercenary, she entered the Officer’s Academy with money loaned from her village. She trains hard and lives frugally every day, so she can repay her village’s money and goodwill. She calls Jeralt, who motivated her to become a mercenary, her master and claims that she’s his top student.</string>
    <string name="rhea_description">The archbishop and supreme ruler of the Church of Seiros, since the time Jeralt was in the Knights of Seiros. She recognises the protagonist’s potential and invites them to the officer’s academy. Although she’s like a kind and loving mother, she has a harsh side that passes judgement on those who oppose the church.</string>
    <string name="manuela_description">An ex-songstress who once stood at the pinnacle of the Mittelfrank opera company in the imperial capital. Now she’s a teacher and doctor in the officer’s academy. She’s been seen lamenting her inability to find the man of her dreams. She’s a bit boorish, but is friendly to her new colleague, the protagonist.</string>
    <string name="hanneman_description">A teacher who’s also researching the “crests” bestowed by the Goddess. He’s usually calm, but when it comes to the crests, he can get absorbed and forget everything. It’s hard for him to contain his curiousity, especially towards the unknown crest that the protagonist bears. Doesn’t really get along with his colleague, Manuela.</string>
    <string name="seteth_description">Assistant to the Archbishop of the Church of Seiros. He’s somebody who values order and discipline; although he respects Rhea’s unprecedented decision to invite the protagonist to the Officer’s Academy, nonetheless he remains wary towards them. He dotes on his young sister Flayn and many of his concerns relate to her, but he can seem a little overprotective.</string>
    <string name="flayn_description">	The younger sister of Seteth, the Archbishop’s assistant. She resides in the monastery, although she’s not a student. She has a calm personality and is carefree towards others, but she can often behave eccentrically when her curiousity takes hold, much to the concern of her older brother.</string>
    <string name="jeritza_description">Full name Jeritza von Hrym. A teacher within the Officer’s Academy. He’s a sword instructor who’s main job is to train others. He dislikes involving himself with others, even straight out rejecting those who try to start an idle conversation with him. He’s a man of many mysteries, but when considering his role as the students’ trainer, his sword skills are undeniable.</string>
    <string name="tomas_description">A man who’s been serving as an archivist at Garreg Mach Monastery for over 40 years. Besides the books within the library, he’s well versed with the monastery’s happenings throughout the years. He’s also a devout follower of the Church of Seiros.</string>
    <string name="cyril_description">	A young boy who acts as one of Archbishop Rhea’s servants. He feels indebted towards Rhea for rescuing him from his troubled life as a war orphan. He takes his work at the monastery extremely seriously, to the point that he gives off a cold impression. To help out Rhea, he studied archery under Shamir.</string>
    <string name="jeralt_description">The protagonist’s father. He’s a veteran warrior who once served as captain of the Knights of Seiros and regarded as the strongest knight in history. After leaving the knights, he continued his journey with his newly established mercenary band. His wife has since passed away. After the students were rescued from the bandit attack, he used the opportunity to return to the knights.</string>
    <string name="catherine_description">	A graduate of the Officer’s Academy at Garreg Mach Monastery, and a member of the Knights of Seiros. She’s a master swordswoman who wields the “Thunderbrand”, one of the legendary weapons referred to as “hero relics”, and a knight who has sworn loyalty to Archbishop Rhea.</string>
    <string name="alois_description">A member of the Knights of Seiros. When Jeralt still served as knight captain, he was one of his subordinates and he’s admired him since then. He gave the protagonist a rare recommendation to become a teacher, after they repelled the bandits that attacked the students. He’s cheerful, friendly and likes telling (bad) jokes.</string>
    <string name="gilbert_description">A member of the Knights of Seiros, hailing from the Holy Kingdom. He’s a pious, serious and polite individual. His expression rarely changes and he tends not to speak of himself. So it’s hard to know his inner thoughts, but he does enjoy fishing and cooking.</string>
    <string name="shamir_description">A bow adept who’s stationed in the Knights of Seiros. She was once a mercenary, but now serves as a knight to repay a debt to Rhea from the past. She’s a rarity within the knights because she’s not a follower of the church; for now, she swears allegiance to Rhea only.</string>
</resources>
